Guide to the Judy Malloy Papers, 1956-2010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Exhibitions, 1970s-2000, (4 boxes)
  - Artists Books (Box 4)
    - Visual Poetry, exhibition, Sao Paolo Municipal Gallery, Sao Paolo, Brazil, Summer 1988 (Box 4)
    - A Book in Hand, exhibition, Arvada Center for the Arts and Humanities, Colorado, September 14-November 19, 1989 (Box 4)
    - ARS Electronica, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous performances, 1990s (Box 4)
    - Multiples, exhibition, Nexus Gallery/Chastain Gallery, Atlanta, Georgia, September 9-October 12, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Lines of Force, exhibition, Bayfront Gallery, San Francisco, Calif., October 5-December 21, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Die Mauer, exhibition, SOCA Gallery, Napa, Calif., November 1990 (Box 4)
    - Scarlet Letters, exhibition, Women's Studio Workshop, Roslindale, New York, February 1991 (Box 4)
    - Boundless Vision, exhibition, Contemporary Bookworks, San Antonio Art Institute, Texas, September 12-October 27, 1991 (Box 4)
    - National Book Arts Conference, San Francisco, Calif., 1991 (Box 4)
    - Photographic Book Art in the United States, exhibition, Texas Women's University, Denton, Texas, 1991-1994 (Box 5)
      Show traveled to the Institute for Contemporary Art (New Orleans), the Washington Center for Photography, the Houston Center for Photography, CameraWork (San Francisco), and others.
    - International Artists Books, exhibition, The National Library of Lisbon, Portugal, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Wit & Wisdom, exhibition, Forum Gallery, Jamestown, New York, May 20-June 17, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Cross-Currents, exhibition, Selby Gallery Ringling School of Art and Design, February 23-March 28, 1992 (Box 5)
      Show also exhibited at U.C. Santa Barbara, Hayward State University, Calif., and others.
    - Shaped Structures, exhibition, Palos Verdes Art Center, Calif., August 6-October 9, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Art (Word) Art, exhibition, Trojanowska Gallery, San Francisco, Calif., October 28-November 17, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Forward Anywhere (with Cathy Marshall), The ADA Show, Artemesia Gallery, Chicago, March 1996 (Box 5)
    - Boundless: West Coast Book Artists of the Seventies, exhibition, San Francisco Center for the Book, Calif., June 8-August 28, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Cartoon Narratives
    These pop conceptual works began in the 1970s and continued with mail art and performances/installations.
    - Slide sheet of cartoon paintings, 1974-1976 (Box 21)
    - Eschew IBM Salesmen and Forget It, 1979 (Box 21)
      Originals of two mail art cartoons.
    - A Year in Reno, 1980 (Box 21)
      Calendars for the Mail Art Network.
    - Private Parts, 1980 (Box 21)
      An early Lucy story.
    - Keep on Blowing, 1981 (Box 21)
      Part of the Eat Your Art Out fundraiser for the University Art Museum in Berkeley. Folder includes bubblegum cards and part of the box that housed them.
    - The Big Zucchini, 1981 (Box 21)
      This cartoon narrative was handed out serially at La Mamelle in San Francisco. The final installment (Ch. 11) was a live performance at La Mamelle in December 1981. Folder includes slides used in the performance, photographs of the performance, and original performance set drawings.
    - Super Lucy, 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 21)
      Series of pop conceptual cartoon handouts and performances. Handouts were distributed via handpainted boxes located at Public Image in New York City and The University Art Museum bookstore in Berkeley, among other places. Includes chapters 1-15 with distribution information (performances, radio broadcasts, and publication) as well as slides, photos, and documentation.
    - 500 3x5 cards and other stories, 1984 (2 copies) (Box 21)
    - Lucy Comes Back, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 21)
      The final installment of the Lucy narratives took place at a party at Malloy's studio on April 20, 1986. Includes story originals, 2 copies of the book distributed at the party, invitations, and maps to the event, as well as information related to an undated and unrealized performance/installation.
    - Bedtime Stories, 1988 (Box 21)
      Malloy would distribute these texts at art events. Folder includes originals and a slide of the handout box.
  - New Media
    - Germany, Die Mauer: US Artists Respond to the Berlin Wall, Nov. 8-Dec. 20, 1990, Soco Gallery, Napa, CA (disk removed) (Box 5)
      A computer program that combined in one list all the cities and towns of both West and East Germany and was displayed alongside a handpainted bucket full of painted and labeled objects and rocks, each representing a German city or town. Folder includes flyers for the show, the exhibition version, the computer program and printouts from the software, slides of the bucket, correspondence with Carl Loeffler and Anna Couey, and material used for research and information.
    - You!, Reflux, Sao Paolo, Brazil, 1991-1993 (Box 5)
      Includes Artur Matuck's catalog for the Reflux Project.
    - The Yellow Bowl, Digital Identities, Sheppard Gallery, University of Nevada, Reno, February 3-March 3, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Objective Connections (with Sonya Rapoport), Generations, Richmond Art Center, Richmond, Calif., September 21-November 16, 1996 (disk removed) (Box 5)
      Authorized edition available at http://www.judymalloy.net/richmond/srapoport.html.
    - Archiving as Art, exhibition, International Symposium on Electronic Art (ISEA 2000), Paris, France, December 2000 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibition Files (Box 25)
    - Fireball, Dog and Cat Show, ASUC Studio, UC Berkeley, Berkeley, CA, March 1981 (Box 21)
      Includes Best of Breed Award, a note to curator Helen Holt explaining Malloy's sculpture, and an audio tape that was part of the sculpture.
    - Looking at You Looking at Me, Gatehouse Gallery di Rosa, 2011-2012 (Box 25)
      Performance documentation of "Free Values," including brochures and notes.
    - "Free Values" posters and publicity, 1988 (Box 26)
    - "How To Play," 1989 (Box 26)
    - Digital Stories of the 1990s: A Look at Works from the Storyspace School, Vancouver, 2012 (Box 25)
    - Istanbul Contemporary Art Museum; Pulp to Pixels, 2012 (Box 25)
      Email and printout from Pulp to Pixels exhibit, Amherst, 2012, and the Istanbul Contemporary Art Museum Web Bienniel, 2005.
    - Monumental Women exhibit poster, 1987 (Box 26)
    - Electronic Literature Organization symposium poster, 2002 (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous exhibit materials (Box 27)
    - Any way you look at it, ADM has your antenna(?) unfinished exhibit (Box 27)
- Talks and Readings, 1982-2004, (2 boxes)
  Includes general public speaking engagements as well as a folder from Malloy's participation in the Telluride Ideas Festival at Deep Creek Camp, Summer 1993.
  - Over the Edge, on KPFA, September 13, 1982 (Box 5)
    Audio tape.
  - General talks and readings, 1982-2004, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    Includes materials from Radical Humor, at the New York University student center, 1982; Hypertext, a reading by Malloy, Christine Tamblyn, and Maria Hernandez, San Francisco Public Library, Park Branch, 1994; and The Impact of Technology on Art, U.C. Davis, where Malloy was a panelist, 1995. Also includes materials from The Women's Leadership Institution, 2001; UC Santa Cruz Hypertext 2004; Wired Women readings; and the State of the Arts Conference at Arizona State from 1994.
  - NCGA Arts Conference, San Jose State, California, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Virtual Museum, August 1991 (Box 11)
    Malloy gave a guest lecture titled "Looking Out the Windows on the Telematic Bus."
  - MLA Convention, New York City, 1992 (Box 5)
    Includes notes and 3x5 cards from Malloy's panel presentation on Hypertext, Hypermedia, Defining a Fictional Form.
  - Telluride Ideas Festival, Deep Creek Camp, Colorado, 1993 (Box 5)
    Malloy was an invited speaker; she spoke about electronic publishing. Includes a press release, notes from her session, flyers for a Deep Creek open house, lists of participants, and other materials.
  - Third Conference on Computers, Freedom and Privacy, Burlingame, CA, March 1993 (Box 11)
    Malloy presented a paper titled "Artist on the Net" on the Imagining Cyberspace panel. Includes invitation and correspondence from Anna Couey about the panel as well as the card index for the talk.
  - Poetry Center Reading series, 1994 (Box 5)
  - The Impact of Technology on Art, UC Davis, April 24, 1995 (Box 11)
    Includes index cards from Malloy's talk, which consisted of extracts from emails between Malloy and Cathy Marshall concerning their paper about Forward Anywhere for the book Wired Woman.
  - Global Information Infrastructure (GII) Awards, San Francisco, CA, December 14, 1999 (Box 11)
    GENID/NEME (Gender and Identity in New Media), a website that Malloy created, was a semi-finalist. The website was a public interactively created document that was structured as a digital conference. Folder includes memorabilia from the GII Awards and printouts from GENID/NEME.
  - Lit[art]ure: Something Old, Something New roundtable discussion printout, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Critical Code Studies Working Group, Humanities and Critical Code Studies Lab, University of Southern California, 2012 (Box 25)
  - Judy Malloy, Retrospective, Electronic Literature Organization conference, 2012 (Box 25)
  - FILE 2012 Electronic Language International Festival, Brazil, 2012 (Box 25)
    Re: From Ireland with Letters.
  - Index card speeches and fragments, undated (Box 11)
- Correspondence, 1940s-2000s, (4 boxes)
  Includes personal correspondence from Malloy's childhood, as well as correspondence between Malloy and her contacts throughout the art world, with both traditional and new media artists.
  - General correspondence (Box 5)
    - Family correspondence, 1943-1993 and undated (Box 19)
      Includes some clippings and ephemera.
    - Letters home from camp, 1950s (Box 19)
    - Trump family, 1960-2003 and undated (Box 19)
      Close friends from Winchester, MA. Folder includes letters, cards, and clippings.
    - Postcards from Europe, 1963-1966 (Box 19)
    - Christmas cards, Ispwich, Mass., 1970s (Box 19)
    - Holiday cards, 1978-2010 and undated (Box 19)
    - Jean Brown (curator), 1980-1984 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, 1981 and undated (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous professional correspondence, 1981-2008 and undated (Box 19)
    - Exhibitions, miscellaneous, 1983-1994 and undated (Box 19)
    - Judith Hoffberg (curator), 1985-1991 (Box 19)
    - Richard Hubbard Howland, 1989-2006 (Box 19)
      Malloy's father's second cousin, an art and architecture historian affiliated with the National Trust for Historic Preservation and the Smithsonian.
    - Logos Foundation, regarding Penelope, 1991-1992 (Box 19)
    - San Francisco Art Institute, letter of appointment and contract, 1996 (Box 19)
    - David Kritt, regarding "Approaches to Creative New Media," 2005 (Box 19)
    - Gale Contemporary Authors, regarding Malloy's inclusion in the series, 2006 (Box 19)
  - Artists correspondence
    Consists of an archive of mailings, clippings, postcards, letters, prints, and original artwork from various book artists, performance artists, and other friends of Malloy, dating largely from the 1970s-1980s. Organized alphabetically by last name.
    - Richard Alpert (Box 5)
    - Anna Banana (Box 5)
    - Berkeley friends (Box 5)
    - John Cage (Box 5)
    - Guglieimo Cavellini (Box 5)
    - Ryosuke Cohen (Box 5)
    - Sas Colby (Box 5)
    - Paul Cotton (Box 5)
    - Martin Cox (Box 5)
    - Cracker Jack Kid (Box 5)
    - Deep Creek and Arizona friends (Box 5)
    - Irene Dogmatic (Box 5)
    - Painted poster of Malloy from Irene Dogmatic (Box 26)
    - Emily DuBois (Box 5)
    - Leonard Frank Duch (Box 5)
    - Steve Durland (Box 5)
    - Terry Ellis and David Mott (Box 5)
    - Jimmy Evans (Box 5)
    - Pat Fish (Box 5)
    - Nancy Frank (Box 5)
    - Bill Gaglione (Box 5)
    - Rich Gold and Marina LaPalma (Box 5)
    - Bruce Handelsman (Box 5)
    - Jo Hanson (Box 5)
    - Jan Henderkrise (Box 5)
    - Ed Higgins (Box 5)
    - Helen Holt (Box 5)
    - Ledger print by Michael Horse (Box 26)
    - Byron Hunt (Box 5)
    - Irwin Irwin (Box 5)
    - Christo Javacheff-Running Fence Project (Box 5)
    - David Jekel (Box 5)
    - Mary Jean Kerton (Box 5)
    - Bengt af Klintberg (Box 5)
    - Robert Leverant (Box 5)
    - Scott MacLeod (Box 5)
    - Vance Martin (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous Mail Art and artists correspondence, (3 folders) (Box 6)
    - Lois Moore (Box 6)
    - Jurgen Olbrich (Box 6)
    - Tom Patrick (Box 6)
    - Michael Peppe (Box 6)
    - Carol Pittore (Box 6)
    - Aviva Rahmani (Box 6)
    - Richard Raxlen (Box 6)
    - Melynda Reid (Box 6)
    - Robert Rockola (Box 6)
    - Domestic Tranquility, by E.B. Rothwell, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Paul Rutkovsky (Box 6)
    - Darryl Sapien (Box 6)
    - Doyle Saylor (Box 6)
    - Jill Scott (Box 6)
    - G.P. Scratz (Box 6)
    - Carolee Schneemann (Box 6)
    - Norman Solomon (6 cent Postage) (Box 6)
    - Lon Spiegelman (Box 6)
    - Jeff Stoll (Box 6)
    - Lynne Tillman (Box 6)
    - Susan Wick (Box 6)
  - ACEN Artists
    - Fortner Anderson (Box 6)
    - Art Com/La Mamelle, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Anna Couey (Box 6)
    - Robert Edgar (Box 6)
    - Carl Loeffler (Box 6)
    - Stephen Moore (Box 6)
      Includes collaborations with Ann Rosenthal.
    - Sonya Rapoport, (includes VHS tape) (Box 7)
    - Howard Rheingold (Box 7)
    - Jim Rosenberg (Box 7)
    - Fred Truck, (2 folders) (Box 7)
- Media by Other Artists, 1985-1996, (2 boxes)
  Software and other media created by other artists. All electronic media has been removed to be transferred to Duke's electronic records server.
  - Robert Edgar: Memory Theatre, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Sonya Rapoport: Shoe-Field (disk removed), c. 1986 (Box 7)
  - Sonya Rapoport: Excerpts from 4 works (videotape), undated (Box 7)
  - Fred Truck: Squared Circle and The Illustrated Art Engine, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Fred Truck: Bottega, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Fred Truck: Mickey Mouse print (Box 26)
  - Brian Thomas: If Monks Had Macs, 1988 (disks removed) (Box 7)
  - Brian Thomas: Hypercard and History, 1993 (disk removed) (Box 7)
  - James Johnson: Second Thoughts, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Fortner Anderson and Henry See: The Odyssey, 1989 (Box 7)
  - La Revue Kaos 1, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Robert Kendall: It All Comes Down To ___, 1990 (disk removed) (Box 7)
  - Robert Kendall: The Clue, 1991 (disks removed) (Box 7)
  - WOE and Carolyn Guyer and Martha Petry, Izme Pass, from Writing on the Edge 2.2 (Spring 1991) (disk removed) (Box 7)
  - Stuart Moulthrop: Victory Garden, 1991 (Box 20)
  - Michael Joyce: Afternoon, 1992 (Box 20)
  - La Revue Kaos 2 (Jan. 1992) (disk removed) (Box 20)
  - Artur Matuck: Reflux Interactive, c. 1992 (disk removed) (Box 20)
    You! was included in this project.
  - Richard Gess: Mahasukha Halo, 1992 (disks removed) (Box 20)
  - Carolyn Gruyer: Quibbling, 1993 and Richard Gess: Mahasukha Halo, 1992 (disk removed) (Box 20)
  - Deena Larsen: Marble Springs, 1993 (disk removed) (Box 20)
  - Jim Rosenberg: Intergrams 1 and 2, 1993 (disks removed) (Box 20)
  - Jim Rosenberg: The Barrier Frames-Diffractions Through, 1996 (Box 20)
  - ApolloMedia: Conduct Unbecoming, 1995 (disk removed) (Box 20)
    Based on Randy Shilts' eponymous 1994 book on gays in the military.
  - Cesium, Artist Collection #1, 1995 (disk removed) (Box 20)
  - Stephanie Strickland: True North, 1997 (disk removed) (Box 20)
  - William Gillespie, Frank Marquardt, Scott Rettberg, and Dirk Stratton: The Unknown: An Anthology, 2002 (CD removed) (Box 20)
  - Tim Perkins: Noisy People: Improvising a Musical Life, 2006 (DVD) (Box 20)
  - Joseph Weintraub: The LIFEPLAN Man, undated (disk removed) (Box 20)
- Personal Materials, (4 boxes)
  Personal photographs and slides, as well as information about Malloy's family and personal documents.
  - Photographs and Slides
    Photographs, slides, and some related material on Malloy and her family. Detailed descriptions available in boxes.
    - Photo album (Box 14)
      Family and friends. Permission is granted to use any of the photos with the exception of the official wedding photos. Most of the photos in this album were taken either by Malloy or by her mother, Barbara Powers.
    - Toyboats (Box 14)
      Sailing toyboats in Cohasset and Berkeley with Malloy, her brother Steve, her grandfather, and her mother. Part of the inspiration for its name was Penelope.
    - Cohasset, Mass. (Box 14)
      Malloy lived with her mother and Lillard grandparents on Cedar Lane during the final years of WWII; their house is described in its name was Penelope. After the war, the Lillards moved to Red Gate Lane in Cohasset.
    - World War II - Crockett, CA (Box 14)
      Malloy's father was stationed here after Pearl Harbor; Malloy and her mother also lived there. Folder includes photos of taken in Crockett and near Camp Hulen, TX as well as a pamphlet about Crockett.
    - Winchester, MA (Box 14)
      Malloy lived with her parents and her brothers Steve and Andy in Winchester ca. 1946-1960. Photos taken by Barbara Powers. Folder includes high school photos of Malloy.
    - Cape Cod (Box 14)
      As a child, Malloy visited Wellfleet, Cape Cod every summer with her family. Photo book taken by Barbara Powers; some are scenes from its name was Penelope.
    - Germany (Box 14)
      Malloy lived in Germany twice during the 1960s. Photos taken by Malloy or by Jim Malloy while she lived in Numberg and worked for Special Services libraries. Includes Special Services ID card for North Bavaria district. Malloy used the setting as a part of L0ve0ne..
    - Colorado (Box 14)
      Malloy lived in Colorado twice: in the late 1960s in Boulder and Pinecliffe, where she worked as a librarian, and in the summers of 1993 and 1994 near Telluride. Tom Barley and the Battle of Dogtown was written in Pinecliffe and The Roar of Destiny includes scenes that are composites of places she lived in Colorado.
    - Hebron, NC (Box 14)
      Photos of "Camp," the place Malloy's grandfather Lillard built on Newfound Lake.
    - Steve and Fran's wedding (Box 14)
      Photos of Malloy's brother Steve's wedding to Fran Noonan.
    - Temple, NH (Box 14)
      Malloy spent 1992 living at her mother's house in Temple, NH. While there she wrote part of The Yellow Bowl, produced Leonardo Electronic News, indexed for the Annual Reviews, and worked on the publication of its name was Penelope. Includes photos and slides of her mother's house.
    - The Southwest (Box 14)
      Includes photos of Albequerque, NM, where Malloy and her then-husband Jim lived in 1971-1972; Los Alamos, NM; San Antonio, TX, where Malloy's Aunt Jane lived; and the area near Phoenix, AZ, where Malloy spent time in 1993 and 1994 while working on Leonardo Electronic News and then for Arts Wire. Malloy wrote name is scibe and part of Forward Anywhere and worked on The Yellow Bowl while in Arizona.
    - Ipswich, MA (Box 14)
      The Malloys lived in Ipswich ca. 1972-1974. Landscape painting in Ipswich is part of the background in where every luminous landscape.
    - Sunnyvale, CA (Box 14)
      The Malloys lived in Sunnyvale in 1974-1975. Includes a photograph of an exhibition by Malloy at the Upstairs Gallery in Sunnyvale; Malloy used the experience of painting and exhibiting art in Dorothy Abrona McCrae.
    - Oakland, CA (Box 14)
      The Malloys lived in Oakland in 1976.
    - Berkeley, CA (Box 14)
      Malloy lived in Berkeley ca. 1977-1985. Her experiences in the art community during this period are a large part of its name was Penelope. Folder includes slides of Malloy working on the Wiggly Bush Meadow project; slides and photos from Malloy's house on Grove Street; a photo of Tahoe; and photos from the Plant Pathology Library at UC Berkeley, where Malloy worked.
    - Art friends (Box 14)
    - Kensington, CA (Box 14)
      Slides from when Malloy and her son lived in Kensington ca. 1986-1990. During this time Malloy first began writing online (for Art Com Electronic Network, at Carl Loeffler's invitation, in 1986) and wrote Uncle Roger, Molasses, and its name was Penelope.
    - El Sobrante, CA (Box 14)
      Malloy has lived in El Sobrante since 1996; most of her work, beginning with The Roar of Destiny, was written here. Folder includes photos of El Sobrante and of nearby camping and hiking trips, which contributed to Dorothy Abrona McCrae.
    - Uncle Pete (Walter Lillard II) (Box 14)
    - Lillard cousins (Box 14)
    - Wedding photos, Barbara Ann Lillard and Wilbur Langdon Powers (Box 15)
      Photos of Malloy's parents' wedding; folder includes press clippings.
    - World War II (Box 15)
      Photos of Crockett, CA, Camp Hulen, TX, and possibly Wilmington, NC (places where Malloy's father was deployed in World War II before being sent overseas).
    - Childhood photos (Box 15)
      Photos of Malloy as a child, mostly taken by her mother.
    - Cohasset, MA (Box 15)
      Malloy and her mother lived in Cohasset with Malloy's maternal grandparents while her father was overseas during WWII; pictures mostly taken by her mother.
    - Hebron, NH (Box 15)
      Slides of "Camp," the family house built by Malloy's maternal grandfather on a lake in NH; slides were used to create the installation Recollection, Heller Gallery, UC Berkeley, March 1-27, 1982.
    - Stephen Langdon Powers (Box 15)
      Malloy's brother, born June 6, 1944. Includes photos of Steve; photos and an article about his first wife, Fran, who died of and was active as an advocate about early onset Alzheimers; and photos of their children Jess and Phil. Except for the wedding photos, most of these were taken by Malloy's mother.
    - Andrew Lillard Powers (Box 15)
      Malloy's autistic brother, born May 17, 1949; most photos taken by Malloy's mother.
    - Powers cousins (Box 15)
      Photos of the children and wife of Malloy's Uncle Walter Powers and a printout of Internet pages about the Velvet Underground when Walter Powers III was in the group.
    - Barbara Lillard Powers (Box 15)
      Assorted photos of Malloy's mother, starting in her childhood and ranging throughout her life, and including a photo of her in Peterborough, NH where she lived until her death.
    - Wilbur Langdon Powers (Box 15)
      Assorted photos of Malloy's father.
    - Judy Malloy (Box 15)
      Includes photos of Malloy with her family; as a child; and with Sean in Albequerque.
    - Hebron, NH (Box 15)
      Photos of family "Camp" in New Hampshire.
    - Arizona and Deep Creek (Box 15)
  - Barbara Lillard Powers (Box 16)
    Materials relating to Malloy's mother. Folder ncludes two copies of birth record; 1936 passport; engagement and wedding notices; correspondence, documents, clippings, and photos from her journalism career (she served as Editor of the Winchester Star and the Somerville Journal as well as Managing Editor of the Somerville Journal, the Cambridge Chronicle, and the Watertown Press, all in Massachusetts); and obituaries.
  - Barbara Lillard Powers - Radcliffe thesis (Box 16)
    "Principles of Unity in Contemporary Art, Design, and Building," submitted 1937.
  - Harvard Magazine, November-December 1999 (Box 16)
    Cover story: "Harvard's Womanless History: It's time to revise." Malloy's mother is featured on the cover, the fourth woman up on the right edge.
  - Wilbur Langdon Powers (Box 16)
    Materials relating to Malloy's father. Folder includes birth record, documentation from his military career, and a biography page from a Dartmouth reunion.
  - Guest Register, Lillard-Powers wedding (Box 16)
  - Ethel Hazen Lillard and Walter Huston Lillard (Box 16)